Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Montana State University Extension Service Records
1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.). Extension Service.
MSU.00021
108.8 linear feet
The Montana State University Extension Service Records consist of annual reports, administrative files, and microfilm records from 1912-1070.
This collection is open for research.
Series 1 County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970
Series 2 Indian Reservation Agents Annual Reports, 1955-1970
Series 3 Special Projects Annual Reports, 1926-1953
Series 4 Specialist Annual Reports, 1917-1968
Series 5 Administration Files, 1945-1968
Series 6 Microfilmed Records from National Archives, 1914-1944
The Extension service originated with the agricultural societies founded in the early days of the American republic which provided educational opportunities for farmers and industrial workers. These agricultural societies were influential in the passage of legislation in 1862, permitting the establishment of Colleges of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts in all states. In 1887, Agricultural Experiment Stations were authorized and the Cooperative Extension Service was established in 1914 by the Smith-Lever Act. In Montana, the first county agents predated this federal legislation, with Milburn L. Wilson assigned to Custer and Dawson Counties, and Carl H. Peterson assigned to Fergus County. Gallatin and Missoula counties were the next to receive agents, and the entire program expanded rapidly in 1917 when the State Defense Council demanded more coverage in response to the United States declaration of war on Germany. Eventually almost every county in Montana had at least one agent assigned, as well as a Home Demonstration Agent. Although primarily agriculturally related in its early years, the major function of the Extension Service evolved to provide informal adult and youth education directed to helping people solve the various problems which they encounter from day to day.
All agents filed annual reports of their activities, detailing any special programs or presentations they may have performed during the year for their constituents. Information occasionally includes crop statistics, livestock statistics, weather summaries, and organizational efforts. These reports were typed in multiple carbon copies, with one sent to the state administration offices, one to Washington, D.C., and one retained by the agent.
The reports in this University Archives accession have been arranged in five series: County Agents, Indian Reservation Agents, Special Projects, Specialists, and Administration. A sixth series of duplicate reports microfilmed from the holdings of the National Archives and Records Administration, forms the last series.
Huntley Project (U.S.); Milk River Project (U.S.); Sun River Irrigation Project (U.S.); Montana State College. Cooperative Extension Service; Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.)-Cooperative Extension
Agricultural extension workers-Montana; Agricultural extension work-Montana; Federal aid to Indians-Montana; Indian reservations-Montana; Indians of North America-Agriculture-Montana; Irrigation projects-Montana
Agriculture; Colleges and Universities; Native Americans; Water and Water Rights; Montana; Bozeman
- County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970; 1
  Over the years as the agency evolved, county extension agents and home demonstration agents have assumed the responsibility to maintain offices where citizens can get information on agriculture, home economics, urban horticulture and related fields. These agents have worked with local people in developing educational programs such as the 4-H clubs, and encouraging local leadership by providing training and encouragement. Inherent in these duties has been a charge to keep accurate records and use them for evaluating the effectiveness of their work by submitting to the state and federal offices annual reports. In early years, the reports were typed with multiple carbon paper duplicates, with the original retained by the county office. The carbon copies sent to Washington, D. C. were eventually transferred to the National Archives where they were retained until 1954 when they were microfilmed and subsequently destroyed. (The microfilmed copies have been placed in Series 6 of this accession.) The folders in this series have been arranged alphabetically by county, and then chronologically within that county sort. Not all counties had an individual agent assigned to them, and in those cases where the agent's responsibilities included more than one county, the first county named has been used for the alphabetical sorting. Although the original folder titles have been retained, the following abbreviations have been used: C.A.=County Agent; H.D.A.=Home Demonstration Agent; A.A.=Associate Agent.
  - Beaverhead County; R. C. McChord, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Beaverhead County; Bernard R. Williams, Lillian Stone, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beaverhead County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beaverhead County; Bernard R. Williams, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beaverhead County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beaverhead County; B. R. Williams, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beaverhead County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beaverhead County; B. R. Williams, C.A., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beaverhead County; Miss Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Beaverhead County; B. R. Williams, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Beaverhead County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beaverhead County; Bernard R. Williams, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Beaverhead County; Gladys Tofte, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles, Beaverhead County; H.D.A. and C.A.'s projects, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Beaverhead County; B. R. Williams, C.A., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Beaverhead County; Gladys Tofte, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Supplement, Beaverhead County; Gladys Tofte, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Beaverhead County; Bernard R. Williams, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Beaverhead County; Gladys Tofte and Eleanor Nelson, H.D.A, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Beaverhead County; B. R. Williams, F.A. Ralston, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Beaverhead County; Eleanor Nelson, H.D.A, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Beaverhead County; F.A. Ralston, C.A., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beaverhead County; Eleanor Nelson, H.D.A, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beaverhead County; F.A. Ralston, C.A., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Beaverhead County; Eleanor Nelson, H.D.A. 12/1/43 to 9/30/44, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Beaverhead County; F.A. Ralston, J. H. Mikkelson, C.A.s, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Beaverhead County; Lois Huffmon, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Beaverhead County; J. H. Mikkelson, C.A., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Beaverhead County; Dillon- Miss Dorothy Embleton, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Beaverhead County; J. H. Mikkelson, C.A., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Beaverhead County; Dorothy Embleton Gallup, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Beaverhead County; J. H. Mikkelson, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Beaverhead County; Dorothy Embleton, Lura B. Penwell, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Beaverhead County; Henry Mikkelson, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura B. Penwell, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Beaverhead County; J. H. Mikkelson, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Beaverhead County; Mrs. Lura Penwell, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Beaverhead County; J. H. Mikkelson, Lura Penwell, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Beaverhead County; Clair A. Michels, Lura B. Penwell, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Beaverhead County; Clair A. Michels, Lura B. Penwell, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Beaverhead County; Clair A. Michels, Lura B. Penwell, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura Penwell, Clair A. Michels, Edwin D. Atkins, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura Penwell, Edwin D. Atkins, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Beaverhead County; Edwin D. Atkins, Lura Penwell, Merle M. Lyda, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura B. Penwell, H.D.A.; Edwin Atkins, C.A., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura Penwell, H.D.A.; Edwin Atkins, Agent; Merle Lyda, At Large, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Beaverhead County; Lura B. Penwell and Edwin D. Atkins, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Beaverhead County; Edwin D. Atkins, Lura B. Penwell, Merle M. Lyda, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Beaverhead County; Merle M. Lyda, Lura B. Penwell, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Beaverhead County; Merle Lyda, Stan Howard, Lura Penwell, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Beaverhead County; Merle M. Lyda, Stanley W. Howard, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Beaverhead County; Merle Lyda, Stanley Howard, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Beaverhead County; Merle Lyda, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Beaverhead County, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14-17)
  - Big Horn County; F. E. McSpadden, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Big Horn County; L. B. Ryman, 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Big Horn County; Martha Eder, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Big Horn County; Martha L. Eder, 1923-1925 (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
  - Big Horn County; Martha L. Eder, C.A., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Big Horn County; Martha L. Eder, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Big Horn County; Martha L. Eder, C.A., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Emergency Report, Big Horn and Treasure Counties; D. C. Jones, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Big Horn County; Geo. W. Gustafson, C.A., 1934-1943 (Box 2, Folder 29-38)
  - Big Horn County; G. W. Gustafson, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Big Horn County; G. W. Gustafson, A. L. Johnson, C.A.s, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Big Horn County; Lois Hodgskiss, H.D.A., 11/1/45 to 11/30/45, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Big Horn County; M. W. Heaphy, C.A., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Big Horn County; Lois Hodgskiss, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Big Horn County; M. W. Heaphy, N. A. Jacobsen, C.A.s, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Big Horn County; Lois Hodgkiss, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Big Horn County; N. A. Jacobsen, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Big Horn County; Lois Hodgskiss Brusven, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Big Horn County; N. A. Jocobsen, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Big Horn County; Clementine Sittel, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Big Horn County; N. A. Jacobsen, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Big Horn County; Clementine Sittel, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Big Horn County; N. A. Jacobsen, 1950 December 1-1951 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Big Horn County; H. M. Kilpatrick, Clementine Sittel, 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 15-20)
  - Big Horn County; Leo F. Kleffner, Clementine Sittel, Donald Woodford, Howard J. Morton, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Big Horn County; Clementine Sittel, H.D.A., Leo F. Kleffner, C.A.; Howard J. Morton, A. A., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Big Horn County; Leo Kleffner, C.A.; Harold Strobel, Clementine Sittel, Ada L. King, Howard J. Morton, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Big Horn County; Leo Kleffner, Harold Strobel, Clementine Sittel, Ada L. King, Howard J. Morton, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Big Horn County; Leo F. Kleffner, Ada L. King, Howard J. Morton, Clementine Sittel, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Big Horn County; Leo F. Kleffner, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Big Horn County, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Big Horn County; Leo F. Kleffner (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
  - Big Horn County, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 31-34)
  - Blaine County; E. R. Jackman, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Blaine County; M. A. Thorfinnson, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
  - Blaine and Phillips Counties; H.D.A., 1919 July-December (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Blaine County; M. A. Thorfinnson, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Blaine County; Barbara E. Heidner and Hazel Myers, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Blaine County; M. A. Thorfinnson, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Blaine County; George W. Gustafson, C.A., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 42-45)
  - Blaine County; Max Legge, C.A., 1926-1928 (Box 3, Folder 46-48)
  - Blaine County; Max Legge, C.A., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Blaine County; Max Legge, Theodore Fosse, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Blaine County; C. H. Challey, C.A., 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Blaine County; C. H. Challey, County Extension Agent, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Supplement to Annual Report; E. G. Ferguson, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Blaine County; E. G. Ferguson, C.A., 1934-1942 (Box 4, Folder 7-15)
  - Blaine County; E. G. Ferguson, Donald Luebbe, C.A.s, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Blaine County; Donald Luebbe, C.A., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Blaine County; Elise Wipf, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Blaine County; Donald Luebbe, C.A., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Blaine County; Elise Wipf, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Blaine County; N. W. Majerus, C.A., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Blaine County; Elise W. Thomas, Mrs. Ada Miller, Chinook, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Blaine County; N. W. Majerus, C.A., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Blaine County; Ada A. Miller, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Blaine County; Ada Miller, Elaine Heleen, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Blaine County; Herb DeVries, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Blaine County; Elaine Heleen, Betty Don McMillan, H.D.A.'s, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Blaine County; Betty Don McMillan, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, Juanita Stearns, 1951-1956 (Box 4, Folder 31-36)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, John P. Biggle, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, Agent; Doyle Stocks, Assoc. Agent; John Biggle, Assoc. Agent, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, C.A.; W. Doyle Stocks, Assoc. Agent, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, Olaf J. Brekke, W. Doyle Stocks, Wayne Gibbson, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, Olaf J. Brekke, Wayne Gibson, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Blaine County; Herbert DeVries, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - Blaine County, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5-8)
  - Broadwater County; W. R. Gordon, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 9-12)
  - Broadwater County; R. E. Ward, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Broadwater County; R. E. Ward, Waldo Zirnstein, C.A.s, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Broadwater County; W. O. Zirnstein, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - Broadwater and Lewis and Clark Counties; W. O. Zirnstein, C.A., 1938-1945 (Box 5, Folder 17-24)
  - Broadwater and Lewis and Clark Counties; C. W. Vaughn, C.A., W. O. Zirnstein, C.A., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Broadwater and Lewis and Clark Counties; C. W. Vaughn, C.A., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Broadwater County; Ted Garnett, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Broadwater County; Edward J. Garnett, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Broadwater County; E. J. Garnett, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Broadwater County; Edward J. Garnett, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Broadwater County; Edward J. Garnett, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Broadwater County; E. J. Garnett, 1953 December 1-1954 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Broadwater County; Stanley W. Howard, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Broadwater County; Stanley W. Howard, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Broadwater County; Stanley W. Howard, William J. Cutler, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Broadwater County; William R. Aldworth, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Broadwater County; William R. Aldworth, Agent, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Broadwater County; Frank A. Carter, Wayne Gibson, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Broadwater County, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Broadwater County; Frank Carter, Wayne Gibson, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Broadwater County; Wayne Gibson, Vic Hoxsey, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Broadwater County; Vic Hoxsey, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Broadwater County; Lee Hart, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13-15)
  - Broadwater County, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 16-19)
  - Carbon County; R. E. Bancroft, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Carbon County; Grace S. Garey, H.D.A., 1925-1928 (Box 6, Folder 21-24)
  - Emergency Report, Carbon County; G. W. Gustafson, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, Emergency Report, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, C.A., 1935-1946 (Box 6, Folder 27-38)
  - Carbon County; Joliet - - Miss Gersilda Guthrie, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, C.A., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Carbon County; Gersilda Guthrie, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Carbon County; Gersilda Guthrie, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Carbon County; Marion Snapp, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Carbon County; Marion Snapp Skorupa, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, Marion Skorupa, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, Beverly Wallace, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, Gene Thayer, W. Doyle Stocks, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Carbon County; O. P. Roberts, W. Doyle Stocks, Joan Monson, Robert Brastrup, Rolland Jorgensen, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, Rolland Jorgensen, Joan Monson, Laurence E. Thayer, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Carbon County; Bob Brastrup, C.A.; Joan Monson, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, C.A.; Joan Monson, H.D.A.; Don Pegg, Agent at Large, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, Joseph Rose, Joan Monson, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, Joan Monson, Lee R. Rovig, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, Hazel Hinman, Charles McKay, Marvin Vincent, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Carbon County; Robert Brastrup, Hazel Hinman, Marvin Vincent, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Carbon County, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 25-29)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; M. A. Thorfinnson, C.A., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Carter; Alberta Coleman, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Carter; Lucille Kelly, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Carter; Lucille Kelly Everds, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Report, Carter and Fallon Counties; Keith Sime, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Keith Sime, C.A., 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 6-8)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; G. J. Zeidler, C.A., 1937-1940 (Box 8, Folder 9-12)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Gibson J. Zeidler, George S. Severson, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; G. S. Severson, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; George S. Severson, C.A., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; G. S. Severson, B. L. Dooley, W. N. Alexander, C.A.s, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; B. L. Dooley, C.A., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; B. L. Dooley, C.A.; E. R. Hoff, C.A., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, C.A., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, 1948-1955 (Box 8, Folder 20-27)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, Lee R. Rovig, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 28-29)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Eugene R. Hoff, C.A., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, C.A.; Sara Kerr, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, Sara Kerr, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Eugene R. Hoff, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, Edison Martin, Dianne Undem, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; E. R. Hoff, Dianne Undem, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Eugene Hoff, Dianne Undem, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties; Eugene Hoff, Linda Giesick, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Carter and Fallon Counties, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5-8)
  - Cascade County; R. A. Blanchard, 1914-1916 (Box 9, Folder 9-11)
  - Cascade County; A. E. Enerson, F. E. MacSpadden, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cascade County; W. B. Sheldon, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cascade County; Alberta Borthwick, H.D.A., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cascade County; Alberta Borthwick, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cascade County; Alberta Borthwick, H.D.A., 1921 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cascade County; Alberta Borthwick, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cascade County; Alberta Borthwick, H.D.A., 1923 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Cascade County; F. E. MacSpadden, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Cascade County; R. E. Cameron, C.A., 1925-1930 (Box 9, Folder 25-30)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cascade County; R. E. Cameron, C.A., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Cascade County; R. E. Cameron, C.A., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Cascade County; R. E. Cameron, C.A., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder, H.D.A., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Cascade County; R. E. Cameron, C.A., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder, Florence Michaelson, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Cascade County; D. P. Thurber, C.A., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cascade County; M. Robina Wylder, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cascade County; D. P. Thurber, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cascade County; Robina Wylder Davis, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cascade County; D. P. Thurber, C.A., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cascade County; Mrs. Robina W. Davis, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cascade County; D. P. Thurber, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cascade County; D. P. Thurber, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, C.A., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, C.A., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cascade County; Florence Johnson, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, C.A., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Cascade County; Claris Brown, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, C.A., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Cascade County; Claris Brown, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, C.A., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cascade County; Great Falls, Alma Ragar, Claris Sparrow, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, C.A., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cascade County; Dora C. Clark, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cascade County; Mrs. Dora C. Smith, H.D.A.; Florence Elliott, Assistant, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)